中文字幕最后修改时间：2020年9月24日
English Subtitles: explosiveskull
中文字幕/特效字幕: MeGustaVerano C.X.
那段历史从未消逝。
它甚至尚未结束。
威廉 福克纳
Em? Darlin'?
呣? 亲爱的?
Get.
驾
Kill me. Kill me.
杀了我  杀了我
Now, don't you worry, girl.
别担心 姑娘
I will accommodate you.
我会让你适应的
How?
怎么...？
No!
不!
《内战前》
梦陷
隶史
I often ponder the depths of your loyalty.
我不太相信你会老实待着
Prove me wrong.
别让我失望
Say your name, girl.
告诉我名字 姑娘
Say your name.
告诉我名字
It brings me no joy to do this.
我这么做也没什么开心
Silence!
安静!
You will speak only when I instruct you to speak.
我让你说话 你才能说话
I am responsible for you now,
现在你归我管
and I will tame your savage ways.
我会让你懂什么是规矩
- Now, get up. - No, no!
- 给我起来   - 不 不!
Come on.
快点
Say your name, girl.
告诉我名字 姑娘
Comply!
听话!
You've given me no choice.
你让我别无选择
Now, please stand up for me.
你给我站起来
No, no, no!
不  不  不!
No, no, no, no, no!
Your friends are dead because of you.
你朋友们因你而死
You know that, right?
你明白的 是吗?
Try to escape again,
你再想逃跑
I'll drag you to the burn shed myself.
我亲手送你去炉屋
Now,
现在
let's try this again.
我再问你一次
Say your name, girl.
你叫什么名字 姑娘
Eden.
艾登
Say your name with pride and conviction!
给我大声清楚地说出来!
Eden. My name is Eden.
艾登  我名叫艾登
That's good, Eden. Real good.
很好 艾登 非常好
Everything will be all right now, and, uh,
现在没你什么事了
you can stop that cryin'.
别再哭了
Maybe I can get away for supper tomorrow.
也许我能赶上明天晚餐
You can make us a chicken.
你能给我们做鸡吃
六周后
Y'all seem easily distracted.
你们很容易走神啊
Why don't we break up this monotony
要不咱们也别那么枯燥
and get y'all focused?
这样容易分心
Go on, sing us somethin'.
来吧 唱点什么
Perhaps one of those old Negro tunes.
或许 来首你们黑鬼的小调
We need to move. These fuckers is crazy.
我们要逃走  这些杂种疯了
Next time, I won't be so generous.
下次我不会这么客气
Back to work. All of you!
你们都继续干活!
Let the sound of Confederate victory bring joy to your labor.
让南方邦联的胜利炮火给你们鼓鼓劲
Milk, chicken.
牛奶  鸡肉
We must try again.
我们必须再试一次
- Get down. Get down! - Get off there. Come on.
- 下车  下车! - 快下车
- Get off the wagon. - Move! Get out of here!
- 从马车上下来  - 快走! 快下去!
What you lookin' at? Line up. Come on!
看什么? 排好队 走啊!
Hurry!
别磨蹭!
Line up! Get over there.
排好队 去那边
Eden!
艾登!
Get your ass down here, girl!
你给我滚过来  姑娘!
Separate yourself. Turn.
分开站好  转身
Look at her hair.
瞧这头发
Quite a beauty.
算长得漂亮
Shall we name her, child?
给她起个名字 孩子?
Mmm... Let's name her Julia.
嗯... 就叫她茱莉亚
Hmm.
嗯~
You hear that?
听见了吗?
Those are worker hands.
这些都是干活的料
You're dismissed.
你可以去玩了
Well,
好了
welcome home, one and all.
欢迎大家回家
Now, listen up! All of you.
现在 都听好了! 你们所有人
This here is a reformer plantation
这里是一个转化型种植园
commandeered by the Ninth Infantry
现在被第九步兵团征用
of the Confederate Army of the 13 states.
隶属于13个州的南方邦联陆军
Wherever you were before,
不管你们以前在哪儿
whatever...
尝到了点...
small freedoms you might have enjoyed,
什么自由的小甜头
I'm here to tell you that's over.
我告诉你们 那都结束了
I don't tolerate any back talk whatsoever from inferiors.
我绝不容忍 下人们在背后窃窃私语
In fact,
实际上
on this plantation,
在这个种植园
you will only speak when given permission to do so.
只有得到许可 你们才能开口说话
That means
也就是说
absolutely no talking among yourselves
你们之间绝对不许讲话
unless one of the white folk on property...
除非这片土地上的白人...
...gives you permission to do so.
...要求你们开口说话
If you do...
你们敢违抗...
Oh.
哦
We will know about it.
我们会知道的
Over here, you will find your cabins.
在这儿 你们都有自己的小屋
You will also be given instructions by one of the overseers as to your daily duties,
工头也会告诉你  每天都干些什么
which ought to be followed obediently
你们要完全地服从
and with a smile.
还得保持微笑
Here, we whistle while we work.
在这儿 我们边干活边哼歌
Ain't that right, Eli?
对不对, 艾利?
Raise the flag, Corporal.
把旗升起来 下士
The general will be home this evening.
将军今晚就回家了
You're dismissed.
解散
Get.
走
Go on. Walk, now.
走  走
Get on. Let's go, move.
跟上  我们走  走
Hey, what is this?
嘿  这是什么地方?
Quiet!
别说话!
Go, now!
快走!
Mmm.
嗯
You started early.
教训吸取得挺快
When?
什么时候?
How many...
多少...
Get in here.
快进来
You're from Virginia, right?
你来自于佛吉尼亚 对吧?
I'm from North Carolina.
我来自北卡罗莱纳
Look, I can't do this.
这我做不到
Whatever you're doin',
无论你们在干什么
I can't do it.
我不会做
Listen to me.
你给我听好
Wherever you came from before here,
无论你之前从哪儿来
- you need to forget about it. - Mmm-mmm.
- 你得把过去都忘了   - 是啊
That is not possible for me.
这对我不可能
What are we doin'?
我们到底在干嘛?
Huh? What is the plan?
到底有什么计划?
You think I haven't tried?
你以为我没试过?
We must choose our moment wisely.
我们必须周密计划
But until then,
但目前而言
we keep our heads down and our mouths shut.
我们只能顺从和闭嘴
Do you understand me?
你明白了么?
I know you.
我认识你
And I know that you are my only way out of here.
而且我知道 你是我离开这里的唯一依靠
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
I need you to listen to me.
你得听我说
You have to keep quiet.
你得保持安静
These white people will kill you.
这些白人会杀了你
Oh, you think being quiet is being strong, huh?
你觉得缄默就显得强大?
What has that ever gotten us?
这给我们带来了什么?
You ain't no leader.
你不是领导者
You're just a talker.
你只是个空谈者
Ain't that right, huh?
说得不对吗?
You...
你...
Hey!
嘿!
What, you just a coward nigger slave
你只是个被烙印的懦弱黑奴
with a brand and no backbone?
丝毫没有骨气
Blood and soil.
血脉与国家
Blood and soil. Blood and soil.
血脉与国家 血脉与国家
As you were.
入座吧
First,
首先
I want to congratulate you
我要恭喜大家
on our defeat of the Yanks at Milliken's.
在米利肯一役 击溃了北方佬
This
这个
is what victory looks like!
就是我们胜利的标志!
We got those blue-bellied bastards on their heels,
我们追着那帮蓝皮猪的屁股
Washington in our sights.
打到华盛顿 指日可待
But we must never relent.
但我们不能松懈
We are descendants of the gods
我们是上帝的子民
and we will fight with the same immeasurable courage and vigor.
我们在战斗中要投入无尽的勇气和力量
We will sacrifice our blood
抛洒我们的热血
and fertilize this soil of our homeland.
染红这片家乡之土
This is the only hope we have
这是我们仅存的希望
of retaining our heritage, our way of lath.
来夺回我们的土地  捍卫我们的制度
This land was always ours.
这土地一直属于我们
It is our rightful inheritance.
有着天经地义的权利
And, rest assured, our nationalist state
请放心  这国家心怀民族大义
will not be stolen from us by these traitors to America.
绝不会被美利坚的叛徒从我们手中偷去
I have faith in this because I have faith in you.
我有此信念 因为对你们有信心
You all are the future.
你们将会是未来
And it is you
也正是你们
who will lead us all to the ultimate victory.
会带领我们走向最终的胜利
But for tonight,
但今晚
let us put away our troubles.
让我们暂时忘却烦恼
Drink and be merry. You've earned it. All of you.
尽享美酒和欢愉 你们值此 所有人
And, by the way,
同时
these Sapphires are here to fulfill your every need,
这些黑珍珠会满足你们的欲求
whatever those needs may be.
无论你们需要她们做什么
Faith! Family! Folk!
信念! 家人! 人民!
As you were.
大家随意吧
So, which one of these girls do you like?
看上哪个了?
What?
什么?
Which one of these girls do you like?
你看中哪个女孩了?
Hey, angel.
嘿 天使
Yeah, you.
对 就你
Come here. I don't bite.
过来  我不咬人
Come on.
过来啊
My compadre here was just telling me
我好友刚刚告诉我
he thinks you're real pretty.
觉得你很漂亮
No, man. No.
不 兄弟 我没
What, you don't think she's pretty? Hmm?
怎么 你觉得她不漂亮?
No, I mean...
不 我是说...
Yeah, of course I do.
对 她的确是
Well, then. She ain't gonna say no. Hmm?
那行 她不能拒绝你 对吧?
Talk to her.
跟她聊聊
You're in charge here.
这里你说了算
Um...
嗯...
Uh... I, um...
呃... 我，嗯...
Well, I...
那好 我...
Oh, just... Fuck's sake.
哦... 真受不了
He will meet you at your cabin immediately following dinner service.
晚餐后 他会马上去你的小屋
You're dismissed as of this moment.
我允许你现在就可以回去
Now, go and prepare for your corporal.
回去为你的下士做些准备
What's that, girl?
什么意思 女孩?
Yes,
是
sir.
长官
That's more like it.
这才像话
Go on, now. Go.
走吧 快去
Well, you enjoy, all right?
行了 好好享受
I'm going around back to the whipping post.
我去逛一圈 回头在鞭刑柱碰头
If I may?
我可以吗?
I never got your name.
我还不知道你叫什么
Daniel. Um...
丹尼尔 嗯...
It's Daniel.
我叫丹尼尔
Well, thank you, Daniel.
好 谢谢 丹尼尔
For earlier.
前面...
You said that I was pretty.
你说我很漂亮
Of course you are. Anyone can see that.
当然  谁都看得出来
It's, um...
已经...
It's just been such a long time since any man has been nice to me.
已经有很长一段时间 没有哪个男人对我这么好了
I appreciate the compliment is all.
非常感激你的赞美之词
你怎么会如此温柔?
How'd you get to be so sweet?
Look, you don't...
瞧  你不必...
You don't have to do this.
你不是非干不可
I can tell that you're special.
我能看出 你很特别
You're not like the others. Those monsters.
你不像其他人 那些禽兽
Why'd you speak to me?
为什么跟我说话?
You mean, when your friend called me over before?
你指, 你朋友叫我过去那会儿?
No. Why'd you speak to me
不是 我刚进屋时候
when I entered the room just now?
你为什么跟我说话?
Uh...
呃...
I just thought we should have a proper introduction.
我只是觉得 该有个合适的开场白
You have a short memory, then.
那你有些健忘了
You heard Commander Jasper.
指挥官杰斯帕说了
You speak only when given permission to do so.
你得到允许才能说话
- Is that not right? - Yes, sir. Uh...
- 我说的对么?   - 是的 长官 呃...
I mean, Daniel.
我是想说 丹尼尔
No. It's "sir"!
不 就该是 "长官"!
You don't know shit! You don't know shit!
你还没搞明白! 你根本不清楚!
Okay.
好的
I'm as much a Confederate as any man here.
我是名南方邦联军人 跟他们一样
Because I don't wanna sleep with no filthy fucking mongrel
我可不想 不觉羞耻地睡一个黑鬼
instead of my own kind, that don't make me no...
却不是白人妞，这并非毫无...
I'm... I'm a patriot! You understand me?
我...我是名爱国者! 你明白?
Shut the fuck up!
给我闭嘴!
Shut up!
闭嘴!
You're lucky I don't tell Jasper.
我不上报杰斯帕 算你走运
You better make him believe I had my way with you
你最好让他相信 你让我称心如意了
if you know what's good for you.
若你有自知之明的话
You understand me?
你明白我意思?
Get off of me.
给我滚开
Uh...
呃...
Sucker.
贱货
Well, you're forgiven your tardiness,
原谅你的迟到
this time.
但仅此一次
Don't make it a habit, or the stocks will be waitin'.
别当成习惯, 否则刑罚等着你
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
Please...
求求你...
I know. Be patient.
我理解 要有耐心
Just keep goin'.
只能继续忍着
We have to keep goin'.
我们都得继续忍着
Oh, no!
哦  不!
No! No, no, no!
不!  不  不  不!
No!
不!
- Oh, no! No! - It's okay.
- 哦 不! 不!    - 不要紧
It's not okay!
这很严重!
Cracker!
杂碎!
The fuck you just say, boy?
你刚才说什么 孩子?
Oh, I'm gonna be right back for you.
我回头再收拾你
Hyah.
驾
What the fuck is the issue?
出了什么事情?
She's sick, sir.
她病了 长官
Oh, no...
哦 不...
Oh... Go on. Go get yourself cleaned up.
哦... 去吧 去把自己清理干净
May I go with her?
我能陪她去吗?
She can handle herself. Get back to work.
她自己能对付 你回去工作
Sir...
长官...
Oh.
呕
Fine. Go clean her up, get back here.
好吧  陪她去吧 弄完了回来
Take hold of him.
牵着马
It's okay, boy.
没事 孩子
Now,
现在
what was that you were sayin',
你前面说什么
boy?
孩子?
Oh.
哦
You missing your woman?
想你的女人了?
Give me an excuse.
给我个理由
Go on.
说啊
No.
没有
Why, that reminds me, the shed needs cleanin'.
提醒我了 那火炉该清理了
Too many foolish Negroes with rebellious hearts.
太多愚蠢的黑鬼想着反抗
Yeah. Go get that cleaned up, boy.
没错 去把那儿清理干净 孩子
That should stop you flappin' them gums.
那能扑灭你切齿的愤怒
Yes,
是
sir.
长官
Yes, sir.
对 长官
Go on, get.
去吧
Cracker-ass cracker.
杂碎中的杂碎
Sweet dreams, Eden.
做个好梦 艾登
Good morning, Steph.
早 斯戴芬
Good morning, V.
早 薇
Just making sure you're ready for your flight.
提醒你别误了航班
Skype is at 8:45,
视讯通话在8:45
and the car will be there at 9:00.
车会在9:00到
- Oh, shit. Okay. All right. - <i>Okay.</i>
-哦 该死 好的 没问题    - <i>好</i>
- Thanks, Steph. Bye. - <i>Safe travels.</i>
- 谢谢 斯戴芬 再见   - <i> 一路顺风</i>
Another bad dream?
又做恶梦了?
No. I'm...
不 我...
I'm okay.
我没事
Babe?
宝贝?
Can you please do me a favor?
能帮个忙吗?
Anything.
尽管说
Can you get Ken Ken dressed for me today?
今天能替我帮坎坎穿衣服么?
Of course. Mmm-hmm.
当然可以 嗯~
My first meeting is right here in Georgetown
我第一场会议就在乔治敦
and it got pushed to 11:00 anyway, so...
又被推到了11:00 所以...
Okay.
好
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm not gonna even be dressed before 9:00.
我9:00前都不一定能整装待发
- I got you. I got you. - Thank you, babe.
-我理解 理解    - 谢谢  宝贝
But
可是...
would it be the worst thing in the world if you didn't make it?
若你没赶上 会是这世上最糟糕的事吗?
Not today. Not today.
今天不行  今天不行
There she is.
小家伙来了
My favorite girl.
我可爱的小姑娘
- Guess what? - What?
- 猜怎么着?  - 什么?
Daddy is gonna get you dressed for school today.
今天爸爸帮你穿去上学的衣服
I know exactly what I want to wear.
我知道我该穿什么了
You do?
是吗?
Hurry up.
快点
- She said "Hurry," Daddy.   -<i> I'm comin', girl.</i>
- 她说 "快点," 爸爸.    - <i>我来了 宝贝</i>
I'm hurryin' I'm hurryin'
我来了, 我来了
Hurry up.
快点
You're gonna pull my arm off.
你快把我胳膊拽断了
Okay, okay, okay.
好  好  好
What you wearin' today?
今天穿什么?
Well, look at you two.
瞧你们两个
Look at you.
瞧瞧你
Mommy loves that dress.
妈妈喜欢这裙子
Excellent choice, baby.
这眼光太棒了 宝贝
Yeah, she picked it.
她自己选的
Hi, babe.
嗨 宝贝
You stay trendin'.
你热度不减啊
Paused it for you.
帮你按了暂停
I understand you think you are defending the plight of the black man.
我理解 你觉得自己在争取黑人的权利
I guess, in your case, the black woman.
当然 按你的说法 是黑人女性
But we are doing a disservice to the argument,
但在此问题上 我们正背道而驰
much less your people...
为数不多的黑人...
by conflating race with basic common sense.
混淆了基本常识和种族概念
I would say this.
我会这么说
The disenfranchisement of black people in America
美国黑人被剥夺公民选举权
is by design, written into the actual DNA of this country.
早已被刻入了这国家的现实基因中
Your argument, however flawed
你的论证 尽管有缺陷
has been successfully promoted and propagated through repetition.
已经被成功地广泛传播 并得到反复提倡
We hear it over and over again.
在我们身边不绝于耳
But I'm here to tell you
但我要提醒你
that this vicious cycle of inequity will soon be broken.
这种不公的恶性循环 很快就会结束
- Boom! - Boom!
- 喯! - 喯!
- 喯!   - 喯!
Boom!
喯!
Mommy, why was that man so angry?
妈妈 为什么那人这么生气?
Oh, baby, that is a really great question.
宝贝 这是个很棒的问题
Sometimes
有时候
what looks like anger
有些人看上去很愤怒
is really just fear.
其实他那是害怕
Things are not always what they appear to be, baby.
事情并不总是看上去那样 宝贝
Does that make sense?
能明白吗?
Do you remember when Vanessa was bullying you at school?
你还记得 薇妮萨在学校欺负你的事吗?
She was pickin' on you?
她只捉弄你
And Mommy had to come up there
妈妈只能去学校
because Vanessa thought that you were gonna come in class
因为薇妮萨觉得 你去了她们班
and take all of her toys away.
会抢走她所有的玩具
And now you two are like best friends.
而现在你们却是最好的朋友
So, are you two friends yet?
那 你们俩现在成朋友了吗?
Not yet, baby.
还没 宝贝
Mommy's working on it.
妈妈在努力
斯贝尔曼学院
哥伦比亚大学
薇罗尼卡 汉莉
美国宪法史博士
哥伦比亚大学
薇罗尼卡 汉莉
美国宪法史博士
Pancake?
煎饼吃吗?
Pancake? On a Tuesday?
煎饼? 在周二吃?
What is the special occasion?
这什么特殊情况?
Well, I was informed it was pancakes or nothing, so, you know,
好吧 我曾被你问 要么煎饼 要么没得吃
we gotta pick our battles.
你懂得 我们又得吵了
Um, question, are we vegan this week?
问你下 我们这周纯素吗?
Babe,
宝贝
the struggle is real.
纠结相当的残酷
Got it. So, one non-vegan pancake coming up.
知道了 一个免蔬煎饼 很快好
Babe, no. I cannot.
宝贝  不 我没时间了
Elizabeth?
伊丽莎白吗?
Yes.
是的
Dr. Henley.
汉莉博士
Hi. And
嗨
please call me Veronica.
请叫我薇罗尼卡
How are you this morning?
早上好啊!
Oh, I'm fine.
我好得很
That lipstick just looks lovely on you.
你那唇色看着很可爱
It suits your skin tone.
跟你肤色很般配
I don't think I could pull it off.
我就驾驭不了
So, do you have any questions for me?
那么 你有什么问题要问我?
How did you come across my work?
你怎么闯进来的?
Oh, I saw you on one of those legacy media networks.
我在那些传统媒体上见过你
I believe it was a roundtable discussion about inclusion.
我确信这是个关于社会包容(杂质)的圆桌讨论
You were so articulate.
你真是伶牙俐齿
It must have been a ratings bonanza.
肯定让你财源滚滚
Those particular segments do garner a lot of attention.
那些专题栏目的确吸引大众目光
I don't mean to be curt,
我不想无礼
but do you have any questions around the book?
关于那本书 你有何见解?
Oh.
哦
Your book.
你的书
Yes, I believe you mentioned it on that show that you were on.
我相信在那档节目中你已经提及
As a matter of fact, I know you mentioned it.
事实上 我知道你提及
'Cause I thought it was rather odd
因为让我奇怪的是
that you chose that moment to be peddlin' your wares.
你居然在那种场合兜售你的私货
Well, actually, that particular segment
事实上 那专题栏目
focused on the lack of inclusion.
就针对社会包容的缺失
And that is exactly what my book highlights.
而那恰巧也是这书的重点
Intersectionality of race, class, and gender.
种族 阶层 性别的交错性
I wrote <i>Shedding the Coping Persona</i> as a road map to revolution
我写《 蜕弃苟活的外衣》旨在为变革引明方向
for historically marginalized people.
也为那些被历史边缘化的人
Maybe I didn't catch this earlier,
可能我一下子想不起来
but who did you say you were with again?
你曾经跟谁一起共事?
I didn't mention it.
我没说
I'm a bit of a talent scout.
我有点类似于伯乐
Oh. So, you're a headhunter. That makes sense.
所以 你是名猎头 我明白了
I'm a headhunter.
我是猎头？
Exactly that.
的确如此
Oh.
哦
Now, is that Kennedi?
哦 那是坎尼迪?
Will you move the camera over? Oh. She's so cute.
快把摄像头转过去 她太可爱了
She'll make a perfect little companion for my daughter.
她跟我女儿能成好姐妹
I see a playdate in our future.
一个未来玩伴已浮现眼前
As my assistant mentioned earlier,
助理曾提醒我
I am short on time this morning.
今天上午我琐事繁忙
Oh, no problem. I didn't mean to trigger you numb.
哦 没问题 我没故意来刺激你麻木的神经
You have fun at your summit, and I'll see you soon.
你尽管在会议上自嗨 我们后会有期
Thank you so much. Thank you.
谢谢 太谢谢了
- Who was that? - Oh, baby.
- 刚那是谁?   - 哦宝贝
It's nobody.
这无关紧要
Don't worry about that woman, okay?
别介意这女人  好么?
Okay.
好
That's my car.
车来了
I can't even imagine what y'all are about to get into.
简直不敢想象 你俩都快要吵起来了
- Obviously. - Mommy, wait.
- 肯定啦   - 妈妈 等等
- I'll call you. I love you. - I almost forgot.
-我会打给你 爱你.   - 我差点忘了
This is for you.
这是给你的
Oh, baby.
哦~  宝贝
This is for Mommy?
这是画给妈妈的?
Ken Ken, I'm putting this with all my important work.
坎坎, 无论到哪我都一定带着它
When you look in the sky and you see that big airplane,
当你望向天空 看见那只大飞机
you'll know that's Mommy, comin' home to you.
你就知道那是妈妈 回来看你了
- Wow. That's a big head. - Daddy. Come on.
- 哇 这头好大   - 爸爸...没有吧
It's not that big.
其实没那么大
And I'm gonna hang it on my wall in my hotel.
我会把它挂在酒店的墙上
Yeah.
对
- Daddy. - Yes?
- 爸爸   - 嗯?
Twenty minutes of screen time.
只给20分钟电视时间
Okay.
好的
- I need you to be strong. - We got you.
- 别心软   - 明白了
Be good.
要乖
Mommy loves you. Come here. Come here. Kiss me.
妈妈爱你 过来 来 亲一下
Give Mommy all the kisses.
多亲亲妈妈
One minute.
超1分钟啦
I'll be back, baby. I'll be back.
我会回来的 宝贝
- Okay, okay. I love you, baby. - Bye. Love you, babe.
- 好好 爱你 宝贝  - 再见 爱你 宝贝
- All right. - All right, be safe.
- 好  - 好, 注意安全
I love you. I'll be back, baby.
爱你 我会回来的 宝贝
Love you more, Mommy.
爱你更多 妈妈
Okay. Release.
好了 释放
And as we begin to gather our thoughts for the day,
当我们开始这一天的冥想
I want you to focus on bringing positivity and light
专注于调动所有的乐观与能量
to each and every situation you may face today.
来面对你今天的每一件事
Visualize yourself
想象自己
addressing any obstacles you might face
与可能遭遇的挫折对话
with the same determination
以你不变的决心
and focus that you brought to your practice today.
以及你为此而赋予的专注
See yourself emerging successful and victorious on the other side.
举目获得成功的你 正站在胜利的彼岸
Namaste.
纳马斯蒂 <i>(印度合十礼)</i>
纳马斯蒂
V! V, girl, I got some tea.
薇! 薇, 我带来了冰茶
You better open this door and let me come and spill it.
你给我快开门 让我进来滋你嘴里
Positivity and light, right?
乐观与能量  是这样么?
- V!  - I'm coming!
-薇!  - 我来了!
No, no. Faster!
不 得快点!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
我来了~ ~ ~ ~ ~
- Hey. How are you? - Hey, babes!
- 嘿 你好吗?   - 嘿 宝贝!
- Good mornting. - Good mornting.
- 早 - 早
How is the number one relationship specialist in the world doing this mornting, doll?
世界第一的情感专家今早过得如何 嗯 娃娃?
True.
千真万确
Well, you know... Ooh, it's hot. Just flourishing.
你知道... 哦太热了 ...生机勃勃
You know, being amazing and fantastic as per usual.
你知道 得保持一贯的迷人和灿烂
- You're looking sharp. Yes. - You know how I do. Thank you.
- 你苗条些了 - 你知道我的方式 谢谢
Oh, hello.
哦 你好啊
Why is it so goddamn hot in here?
怎么这里那么热?
I'm trying to create my own version of Bikram.
我正尝试一种自己的高温瑜伽
You know I need all the balance I can get.
我需要达到自己平衡的极致
Well, speaking of balance,
说到平衡
I saw you balance and tag that ass last night on TV, girl.
我见识了 昨晚在电视上给那混球贴满了标签
You got him all the way together.
你完全击败了他
- Bye. - Bye. Thank you.
- 再见    - 再见 谢谢
Okay. Before we get down to it,
好 先关心一下
how is my favorite little human in the world, Miss Kennedi?
坎尼迪女士 世上我最爱的小朋友 她怎么样了?
She's great. She's doing good. Yesterday was tough, though.
她很好 很棒 尽管昨天有点难受
- It was tough. - I just... Ugh.
的确很难受  我只是...
It breaks my heart every time I have to leave her.
每次离开她总有心碎的感觉
Mmm. Ken Ken.
嗯 坎坎
I just feel like I'm not doing enough.
我感觉自己做得不够
It's like when I'm at home, I'm not working enough.
总感觉 我顾了家 没顾上工作
When I'm working, I'm not home enough.
顾了工作 又没顾上家
I'm not Mom enough. I'm not wife enough.
母亲没做好 妻子也没做好
Mmm-mmm, mmm-mmm-mmm.
呣呣 呣呣 呣呣
Okay, you listen to me now. Okay?
好 你听我说 行吧?
Yes, you're a superwoman, but you're also a human woman.
没错 你是个超级女人 可也是个普通女人
Okay? And you are doing awesome.
你干得很出色
And Miss Kennedi,
坎尼迪女士
or as the world will one day refer to her,
或者有朝一日世界恭称她
Madam President,
总统夫人
is living her best life thanks to you, okay?
是否她的成就有恩于你 懂了吗?
So be nicer to yourself, please.
所以 对你自己好一点 行吗
- Thank you. I love you. - Mmm-hmm. I love you, too.
- 谢谢 我爱你   - 呣 我也爱你
Now...
现在...
So, Camille's hostididy ass, right?
那么 卡米尔主持会议 对吧?
- You, girl... - Oh, girl.
- 你这个姑娘 ... - 哦 姑娘
- ...Camille was in the... - Babe, I can't. I can't.
- ...卡米尔她曾... - 宝贝 不行 不行
I... You know I usually would,
我... 你知道我通常会
but I have to get to this walk-through.
可现在我只能袖手旁观
I'm already runnin' behind.
我已经时过境迁了
No, I get it. You're too good for it today.
不 我明白 如今你看不上了
No, I get it. You tryin' to <i>namaste</i> in a peaceful space.
不对 我知道了 你想安静地练“纳马斯蒂”
And I'm about to ruin that, so let me just see myself out.
我差点搅了你的修行 我还是赶快闪了吧
♪ I love you, I love you I love you ♪
♪ 我爱你 我爱你 我爱你 ♪
You're welcome for this free coffee.
很荣幸给您分享免费咖啡
I paid $74.93 for that.
为此我还花了$74.93
No, you did not.
不 你没付
I will Cash App you.
我要把钱收回来
I will. I will. I will.
我会的 我会的 我会的
Stop. All right.
别说了 好吧
All right. And...
好啦  另外...
I wanna remind you to be good to yourself, okay?
告诫你对自己好一点 懂吗?
Be kind to yourself.
对自己仁慈些
All right.
好的
Be kind to my friend.
对我朋友仁慈些
I will.
我会的
I love you.
我爱你
I love you, too.
我也爱你
All right, I'll see you downstairs. Bye.
行了 到时候楼下见 再见
Girl.
这姑娘
Ms. Henley?
汉莉女士?
Yes?
是的?
Delivery.
有您闪送
Oh.
哦
The front desk didn't even call.
前台也没通知我
Who are these from?
谁送来的?
杰斐逊套房                        .
期待您回家
V! Oh, my God.
哦  薇! 哦天呐
Sarah Bee!
萨拉 比!
I'm so sorry. I did not mean to scare you.
抱歉 没想故意吓你
It's okay. I have just been so jumpy this morning.
没事 今早我一直有点神经质
I guess it's travel or something.
估计是旅途累的
Okay, I love you, but I have to run to my panel
行 我想你 可我赶着去座谈会
"The Exorcism of the Unconscious Past."
"驱散沉睡中的心魔"
Ah.
啊
"The past is never dead."
"历史从未消逝"
"It's not even past."
"它甚至尚未结束"
You know, my N.A.N.A. used to say,
你知道 我们北美报盟常说
"Our ancestors haunt our dreams "to see themselves forward."
祖辈们以“与时俱进" 来重塑我们的梦魇
The unresolved past can certainly wreak havoc on the present.
未决的历史定会在当下肆虐
Listen, have an amazing panel. You're gonna be incredible.
祝你有个超棒的座谈会  你一定无以伦比
- I'll see you later, girl. - I'll see you tonight, babe.
- 回头见 亲爱的   - 晚上见 宝贝
Love you.
爱你
Hi.
嗨
Can I please make a reservation at Stefano's tonight?
能为我预定一张今晚在“斯特凡诺”餐厅的桌子么?
Concierge.
礼宾台
Of course. Working on it as we speak.
当然 照我们说好的做
What can I do for you?
能为您做什么?
May I make a reservation for three at Stefano's?
帮我预定一张在“斯特凡诺”餐厅的三人桌
Um, let's say around 7:30.
晚上7点半就行
And I'm in the Jefferson Suite.
我住杰斐逊套房
Sure.
没问题
God bless.
上帝保佑
Oh, shoot.
哦 真倒霉
Puddin', I left my key in the room. Do you mind?
服务生  我钥匙忘在里面了 能帮个忙吗?
You know, I learned very quickly
我很快地意识到
that black people, black women in particular,
我们黑人 特别是黑人女性
we're expected to be seen, not heard.
我们虽随处可见 却不被倾听
Or we risk being perceived as threatening to the patriarchy.
或者 承担着威胁到男权社会的风险
Or, God forbid,
或者 稍有好转
we continue to get branded as the "angry black woman."
我们仍继续被冠以 "愤怒的非洲女人"
Yes.
对
So, the coping persona has been this mode of survival
因此, 苟活的外衣便成为一种生存法则
for generations of oppressed people.
延续了数代受压迫的黑人
What I also learned through those experiences
通过她们的经历 我还意识到
is within our authenticity lies our real power.
在我们的本真性中蕴藏着巨大力量
Yes.
对
And that's even in those environments,
而且 它更弥漫于我们身边
which by design,
早有预谋地
demand our complete and total assimilation.
要将我们完全、彻底地同化
To the patriarchy, we've been practically invisible.
在男权社会中 我们实质上被忽视
But their arrogance is their greatest vulnerability.
他们的傲慢 暗示着他们极度的脆弱
And our greatest opportunity.
却是我们最大的机遇
Yes.
对
And it brings me to a quote
这让我想起一句格言
by Assata Shakur.
出自 阿萨达·夏酷尔
"The only thing that we have to lose
“我们唯一所要摆脱的”
"are our chains."
"只是我们的枷锁"
Liberation over assimilation.
求解放 弃同化
They're stuck in the past.
它曾经如鲠在咽
We are the future.
我们将是未来
Yes.
对
Our time is now.
我们的时代来临了
It's now.
到来了
Right now.
就现在
Just a reminder, you can pick up
提示一下 诸位可以在出门前
<i>Shedding the Coping Persona</i> on your way out.
带上一本《蜕弃苟活的外衣》
Twenty percent goes to HBCU schools
20%的款项 将会捐给 美国黑人大学 所属院校
including Louisiana's own
包括路易斯安那自己的
Dillard and Southern Universities.
迪拉德大学和南方大学
The way that you talked to them, the nuance,
卡米尔：你跟她们沟通的方式 那种细微差别
and there's a specificity that I just can't...
而且有种特性我无法...
Oh, my God. That was fantastic.
哦 上帝 那简直太棒了
So sorry. That was really great, you know.
抱歉  那真的很精彩
I really enjoyed my session,
我真的听的很投入
but I'm really glad I stayed for that.
但我很高兴演讲我在场
Wasn't that fantastic?
很精彩对么?
It was.
的确是
- Camille, this is... - I'm sorry, did I interrupt?
- 卡米尔 这位是... - 抱歉我有打断你们吗?
No...
没有...
I'm gonna continue to.
我得接着说
I really have to steal her. Sorry to be abrupt.
我真得带她走了 抱歉打断
I'll call you.
回头打给你
Okay.
好的
Thank you again.
再次谢谢
I'm just gonna finish up work and get back to... Bye.
我得干完这些事情然后返回... 再见
- Thank you, love. - Great. Bye.
- 谢谢 亲爱的   - 很好 再见
You're welcome.
不客气
Girl, I could feel her angling in on our dinner tonight.
姐 我感觉她想挤进我们的晚餐
And no thank you. She needs to go sit down some place.
哦不谢了 她自己另找地方
Plus, we could use a break from academia.
再说 我们本可以利用这学术间隙
And also, how often do I get my V?
另外  多久我才能见着一次我的薇?
Twice a year?
两年一次?
- Maybe three times a year. - I know, I know, I know.
- 也许三年一次   - 我明白
Okay, I need you all to myself tonight. Okay?
懂吗 我要你今晚完全做回自己 行吗?
No filter. Full Dawn.
无拘无束 通宵达旦
Oh, she comes with a filter?
哦 她带着拘束而来?
Also, after dinner...
还有 晚餐之后...
Yeah.
耶~
You know, when we leave dinner, it's on.
你懂的 我们晚餐结束 激情开启
We gonna be out in these streets body rolling.
我们在那街上就开始嗨
- Oh, dinner. Tonight? - Yes.
- 哦晚餐 今晚? - 没错
I'm sorry, but I have a date with my king bed tonight.
抱歉 可今晚我已经跟我的大床约好了
I won't be joining.
我不参加了
Whack. Wow.
扫兴 哇
No. I have a 6:00 a.m. flight.
不 我要赶早6:00的航班
I promised Ken Ken I'd take her to Katie's birthday party.
我答应坎坎去凯迪的生日会
Okay. All right. It's fine.
好吧 也行
We will keep you abreast of all of our hoetivities via text anyhow.
那手机互动 你和我们的色情活动保持同步
Please do. I wanna know everything.
必须的 我想知道每个细节
Girl, the hoetivity is gonna be popping tonight.
姐 那色情活动会在今晚达到高潮
Girl, meet me down here at 7:00 p.m.
姐 晚上7:00在楼下见
We'll Uber over, okay?
我们叫优步过去
Yes, 7:00 p.m. And I have to go get dressed.
好 晚7:00 我得去换套衣服
Oh, speaking of getting dressed,
说到衣服
what are you wearing tonight?
你打算今晚穿什么?
Do not come down here in mom jeans, okay?
千万别穿大妈牛仔下楼 明白?
I need all eyes on our table
我们桌必须引人注目
'cause I'm tryin' to fuck tonight.
我可打算跟人上床的
You are on board for that, okay?
你也在列 知道么?
I won't disappoint. Bye, girl.
不会让你失望 再见 姑娘
Well, hi. Don't you look beautiful?
嗨 你长得好漂亮
Are you going to the 49th floor, too?
你也去49层?
Shh.
嘘~
You'll get in trouble for talking.
你说话会有麻烦
I'll get...
我会...
Oh. I'll get in trouble for talking? Okay.
哦 我说话会有麻烦? 好吧
Shh.
嘘~
Okay.
好吧
You rang, darling?
你心动么, 亲爱的?
Girl, I said "Step it up," not murder these hoes.
姐 我说了 "跟上节奏"  没让你把我们赶尽杀绝
Mmm-mmm.
呣~呣
Okay. Here's a new concept. What do you think?
有个新概念 说你听听
Instead of a "fuckboy," it's an "inti-mate."
不再是 "操他" 而是 "亲密伴侣"
Okay, I love everything about it.
我觉得怎么都好
注定要成为马术冠军
像她妈妈一样
It's someone who's gonna feed me ice cream
就是既有人喂我冰淇淋
and knows how to soothe my childhood trauma.
也懂得抚平我儿时创伤
It doesn't sound like you need to take a Plan B with that guy at all.
听上去不太像 你想跟他有孩子的样子
An inti-mate..
一对亲密伙伴...
I just want somebody to snuggle me at night. That's all I want.
我只求晚上有人依偎  仅此而已
You deserve.
你值得拥有
- Is that so much to ask? - You can call me.
- 这要求高么?   - 你找我好啦
你们在街上?
你看着性感么?
你露点了么?
You're a great snuggler.
你很擅长依偎
- I am a great snuggler. - Oh, my God.
- 我依偎很棒的    - 哦 上帝
What are you smiling at? Who's that?
你又在笑什么? 这谁啊?
Well, you know it's Nick.
你知道 她总是尼克
Let's see. Dick pics or no?
让我看看 有裸照么?
Aw.
哦
Yeah.
不错
See, here I thought marital bliss was an oxymoron.
看到这儿 我觉得美满的婚姻是个矛盾的说法
Guys, I can 100% confirm that Nick is not that perfect.
诸位 我百分百确定尼克不是完美男人
Trust, okay?
相信我
- But he is kind of perfect for me. - Yeah.
- 但对我来说却是   - 没错
- Ugh. Girl, she ruined it. - There it is.
- 呕~ 姐 被你毁了  - 就是这样
I thought there was tea coming.
我觉得茶要上翻了
I miss my babies, okay?
我想我宝贝 不行么?
I'd miss him, too.
我也想他
谢谢送来的手工花束
"I miss my baby.
" 我想我的宝贝 "
- "Oh, he's so perfect for me." - Please, guys.
- " 哦 他对我是完美的 "   - 别闹了
"He's so perfect for me.
" 他对我是完美的 "
"He's my lobster.
" 他是我的龙虾 "
"He's the Chandler Bing to my Monica."
"他是钱德勒·宾 对于我的莫妮卡"
"He fits perfectly in my little box."
" 他正好能塞进我的小盒子 "
很乐意担此美名
肯定是你粉丝送的
"Like a puzzle piece."
" 像个小迷宫 "
Yeah, no, we're very happy for you, bitch.
没错 不 我们为你感到幸福 贱人
- All right. Time to live in the present. - Okay, babe.
- 行啦 回到现实中来  - 好的 宝贝
- Yeah. - Okay, okay.
- 对啊   - 好 好
Damn.
见鬼!
- Oh, my God. Okay. - Shit, are you okay? Holy...
- 哦 上帝  - 你没事吧? 简直...
Hi. Henley for three, please.
嗨 汉莉预定的三位 谢谢
We have your table. Follow me.
已经预留好了 请跟我来
- Enjoy your dinner. - Uh-uh. No, no, no, no.
- 请在此就坐    - 啊 不 不 不行
Sorry, I think what my friend is trying to say is that...
抱歉 我想我朋友要表达的是...
Actually, babe, I got it.
事实上 宝贝 我明白
This table is 100% not acceptable,
这桌位百分百无法接受
and I think that you know that, don't you...
我想你应该明白 不是么...
...Becky? Mmm-hmm.
...“贝琪”? 呣~
Listen, I'm actually not gonna go back and forth with you about exactly why this table's unacceptable.
听着 我不想跟你在这桌位如何不适上绕口舌
You're gonna seat us over there.
你让我们坐那儿
Oh, um...
哦 呃...
Thank you so much, Rebecca!
多谢啦! 瑞贝卡
You're doing great!
你太棒了!
Yo, get your sis. The Caucasity!
看我们好欺负  白人至上主义!
- No, this is good. - Well, then you're welcome.
- 现在 这里不错   - 不客气
- Welcome. - Hi.
- 欢迎光临  - 嗨
- Wine list. Hi. - Thank you.
- 这是酒单    - 谢谢
My name is Sam. I'll be taking care of you this evening.
我是赛姆 今晚由我为诸位服务
- Will a fourth be joining you? - No, just us.
- 一共是四位吗? - 不 就我们
Very good.
很好
And may I start you off with a cocktail?
要先来杯鸡尾酒吗?
Actually, we will share a bottle of champagne.
其实 我们打算共饮一瓶香槟
How about a nice bottle of prosecco?
来一瓶上好的普洛赛克 如何?
A bottle of Armand de Brignac, please. Thank you.
请来一瓶黑桃A香槟 谢谢
Okay, but more to the point,
行了 说说重头戏
do you have any apt prospects for the night?
聚会后有何节目?
Mmm.
呣
Booked and busy, actually.
早有预定 实际上
Actually, okay, so there's this, um...
实际上 好 事情是这样 呣...
Ooh, I've been trying to set up a meeting with this guy, Justin.
我打算跟一个男的会面 叫贾斯汀
Fine. Just like a dark chocolate,
人很好  就像黑巧克力
like a 72% cacao, you know?
含72%的可可粉那种 明白么?
Just... Chef kiss.
就像... 回味无穷
- Is he fine? - Yes, he's fine.
- 他人好么?    - 对 他人很好
- Mmm. - And he's got a friend.
- 呣    - 他还有个朋友
- For me, a friend? - Yeah, for you.
- 发给我 一个朋友?   - 对 给你
- Mmm. A friend? - Mmm-hmm.
- 呣  一个朋友?   - 没错
I don't know. That sounds sort of suspicious.
我不清楚 这听来不太靠谱
Like, it can't be good.
听上去不妙
I feel like you're leading me into the snake den with this.
感觉像你带我进入蛇窝
Girl, I'm sure he's fine.
我确定他人没问题
- You're sure? - Oh, my God.
- 你确定? - 哦天呐
- You're sure he's fine? - You haven't even met him?
- 你肯定他没问题?  - 你都没见过他?
No, I haven't met him.
不 我没见过他
Nope. This is exactly what is not happening.
不行 这绝对不行
- I am too grown for this. - It's not...
- 我太有经验了 - 这不是...
Okay, you're too grown.
行 你有经验
No, got it. I feel blocked.
我明白了
I do. And that's okay. 'Cause you're grown.
我接受 这没问题 因为你有经验
That's cool. It'll just be you and me tonight
那行 今晚就只有你我一起
and I will meet up with fine-ass Justin some other time.
我会跟贾斯汀 另选时间见面
And maybe his friend, too.
或许还有他朋友
Hey.
嘿
Okay. Do not look.
好  别张望
There is a guy at the bar...
有个男人在吧台...
I said don't look.
我说别看
...that has been staring at us the entire night,
...已经在那盯着我们看一晚上了
and it's creeping me out.
真有些瘆人
Excuse me, ladies. Before we order entrees,
打扰了 女士们 在我们点主菜前
I wanted to let you know that the gentleman at the bar
我想让您知道在吧台那里的男士
sent this drink specifically for you.
特地给您点了这杯酒饮
Oh.
哦
Specifically for me.
特地给我点的
Oh, my God. He's coming over here.
上帝 他朝这边走来了
And he's coming this way.
还走过来了
Okay, all right.
好吧
Pardon me, ladies.
打扰了 女士们
I've had my eye on you.
我注意到了您
I just had to come by and tell you
我只是想过来告诉您
that I think you're quite stunning.
我觉得您非常的夺目
Oh, thank you.
哦 谢谢
Oh, gosh, I'm so flattered, thank you.
哦天呐 我受宠若惊 谢谢
You are extremely handsome yourself.
您也是非常的英俊
Thanks.
谢谢
However, um,
不过 呣~
I'd be remiss if I didn't take the chance to sort of
如果我不对您的小把戏提出点小批评
critique your game just a little bit.
我会觉得对您不负责任
I'm sure that you can tell,
我确定您很清楚
even from all the way over there,
即使在那么远
that we're actually drinking champagne tonight.
我们整晚都在喝香槟
I am a champagne lady,
我是一名香槟女孩
and we are champagne ladies.
而我们则是香槟姐妹
So, sending over a vodka-cran, yeah,
所以  这么送来一杯蔓越莓伏特加 对
it just shows lack of appreciation for our situation tonight, so...
这就显得 您对我们今晚的动态 缺乏了点赏析  所以...
Well, what you should have done is
您可以做的倒是
you should have asked our waiter,
询问我们的侍应生
which, again, champagne we're drinking,
我们喝的是哪种香槟
and sent over a second bottle of it for all of us.
然后给我们再送一瓶
And then, you make eye contact with me from across the room.
而之后 您便可以用目光 穿过这间屋子
You eye-fuck me.
将我细细把玩
Oh, my God.
哦天呐
And I say all that to say,
我说了那么多
Oop, here's my number.
这是我的号码
Because this can happen.
因为 这可以给你
Good night.
晚安
Oh.
哦
Why did you do him like that?
为何这么捉弄他?
You know why I did him like that. He needed to know.
你知道为什么 他应该知道
Okay, I'm sorry, but can we just take a second to acknowledge that that guy was supernaturally fine.
抱歉 我们能否先承认 那男人其实是很不错的
Yeah, he was really cute.
是的 他很可爱
So? I'm cute, too.
所以呢? 我也是
That's true.
没错
- You are cute. - Yeah.
- 你也可爱  - 对
Hey, to being cute and classy.
为可爱和优雅干一杯
- Yes. To being cute. - To being fine as fuck.
- 好 为了可爱   - 为了能睡
Well, I definitely look forward to catching up on this saga.
我绝对期待这样一种场景
On a group text, in my bed.
躺在床上 群发聊天
Very safe move.
非常安全
Wait. Although, this hotel has been so off.
等等 这家酒店真是差到极点
The front desk. They didn't clean my room.
那礼宾台 她们又不清理房间
So, I'm not even holding my breath for turndown service.
我都不记得 自己有拒绝清理房间这事
It's probably a mess.
也许记错了
Really? That's so strange.
真的吗? 那真奇怪了
My service has been impeccable.
我的客房服务无可挑剔
I got the Uber, but I can't believe we're splitting up.
我叫了优步, 真不敢相信我们要分手了
- I know. I'm so sorry. - Oh, no, no, no.
- 我明白 真抱歉   -哦 不 不
Before we split up, we have to take a selfie.
分手之前 一起来个自拍
- Oh, yes. - Let's get a picture.
- 好.  - 我们拍张照
Because it did not happen if it didn't happen...
因为没拍照就等于没聚会...
- You are right about that. - ...in a selfie.
- 你说的有理  - ...来个自拍
Where's my lipstick?
我唇膏哪去了?
- Girl, you look fine. - Your lips look fine.
- 你看着很好    - 你唇色可以
No, but I put it in there.
不 我明明放在里面
- I could've sworn. - Come on, come on.
- 我发誓 - 快 快
- Okay. - Get ready and...
- 好吧 - 准备好...
- All right, that's it. - Tag me in that.
- 好 就这样    - 给我标上
One-take wonders. Everything.
一步 美颜 搞定
I love y'all.
我爱你们
Thank you so much.
谢谢
One moment.
稍等一下
- Love you. - I love you.
- 爱你   - 我爱你
I'm so proud of you.
真为你高兴
- I love you. Get home safely. - I love you so much.
- 我爱你 安全到家  - 太爱你了
All right. I hate I have to go.
好 真不愿分手
I have to get home to my baby, though.
但我得回家看宝贝了
Say hi to the family.
替我问好
All right. Love y'all. Watch her.
好 爱你们  看好她
- You watch yourself. - All night.
- 你自己当心   - 好
- Watch her. - You're doing trouble.
- 看好她  - 尽多管闲事
- Bye. - Bye.
- 再见  - 再见
Goodbye. Is this our car?
再见 那是我们的车?
This is us. Let's go.
是我们的车 我们走
The Montgomery Hotel, please. I think I put it in.
去蒙哥马利酒店 谢谢 你应该收到的
And do you mind turning that down just a bit?
能把音量调低些么?
Thank you.
谢谢
她已经和司机撩起来了
再次谢谢晚餐
First off, that we are some 5-star ladies.
首先 我们是五颗星的淑女
Aren't we, sister?
对不 姐?
And I just wanted to comment
我只是想评价
that you look like a 5-star gentleman.
你看上去像五颗星绅士
- Don't touch him. - Is that too much?
- 别碰他   - 这过分吗?
- Don't touch him. - I know.
- 别碰他   - 我知道
- I wanna have five stars. - It's too much.
- 我想要保持五颗星  - 这过分了
I feel like that was too much. I shouldn't... I'm sorry, Gus.
我也觉得这实在过分了 我不应该... 对不起, 帅哥
I'm so sorry, Gary.
我非常抱歉  盖瑞
Hey, put your... Can you turn that up?
嘿 把你的... 音量调高
- Hello? - <i>Hello, Veronica?</i>
- 喂?    - 喂, 薇罗尼卡么?
Who is this?
是哪位?
♪ Blame it on my juice ♪
♪ 全怪我果汁 ♪
♪ Blame it, blame it on my juice ♪
♪ 全怪  全怪  全怪我果汁 ♪
Come on, on toast
跟上, ♪ 我土司 ♪
♪ Ya-ya eee ♪
♪ 呀-呀-咦 ♪
Wait, hold on, yo, hold on.
等等 等等
♪ Ya-ya-hold, ya-ya-hold ♪
♪ 呀-呀-吼    呀-呀-吼 ♪
<i>This is Autumn, your Uber driver.</i>
<i>我是奥腾, 你的优步司机</i>
- Oh, there must be... - <i>I'm outside of Stefano's.</i>
- 哦 一定是搞... - <i>我在餐厅门口</i>
Yeah, there must be a mistake. I'm in my car right now.
那一定是搞错了 我已经在车上了
I'm outside the restaurant.
我在餐厅门口
No, there's a mistake. I'm here now.
不 一定是搞错了 我已经走了
- <i>Okay, whatever.</i> - Thank you.
- <i>好吧 随便吧</i> - 谢谢
Ma'am, do you mind turning down the music, please?
女士 你能把音乐调低吗 谢谢?
Hello!
嘿!
Turns out, this color does look nice on me.
发现了 这颜色还挺适合我的
Help! Help!
救命! 救命!
What do you want? It's 3:00 a.m.
你想干嘛?  现在是半夜三点
The arrangements are already being made.
都安排好了
Now, look, the ballot box will go our way.
瞧 现在投票权在我们手里
The court will follow one way or another.
不管怎样法庭都会接受
It's under control. Is there anything else?
都搞定了 还有其他事吗?
Oh, really?
真的?
If I see her pathetic husband on the news one more time
让我在新闻里 再看见她可怜的丈夫
parading around that little girl...
带着小女孩游行...
Mouthy darkies are a plague.
多嘴的黑鬼们就是场瘟疫
I'll take care of it.
我来处理
I said I will fucking take care of it.
我说他妈的我来处理它
Eden?
艾登?
They will never take you away from me.
他们不能把你从我身边带走
What'd I say?
我说过什么?
What the fuck did I say?
记得我说过什么?
I told her yesterday she got one pass.
我昨天告诉她 仅此一次
Now she thinks she can come down to the fields whenever she goddamn pleases.
现在她觉得下地干活 可以由着心情？
Well, she will learn her lesson today.
今天得给她点教训
Girl, go get her.
姑娘 去找她
I can head up there, sir.
我可以去 长官
Who gave you permission to speak, boy?
谁允许你说话的 孩子?
I gave myself permission to speak.
我给我自己的权利
Tonight.
就今晚
We go tonight.
我们今晚就走
I'm here.
我在这儿
No, no, no...
不 不 不...
- Are you ready? - Let's go.
-准备好了?    - 我们走
Wait. Wait.
等等
Well, I'll be damned.
我真该死
You're killing me, man.
真要我命了 伙计
Hey, dude, what the hell?
嘿 伙计 这什么?
Hey, is this yours?
嘿 这是你的?
No, Purcell,
不是 普赛拉
you know I know the rules, man. No cell phones.
你知道规矩 伙计 不准带手机
- You fucking cuck. - No cell... What?
- 你这傻瓜  - 不准有手... 怎么了?
Don't say my fucking name out here, Daniel!
别在这儿叫我名字 丹尼尔!
I'm sorry.
对不起
I don't fucking want it.
我可不想要
All right.
行
You should have seen your face.
瞧瞧你刚才的脸色
Yeah, I'm mad.
我快疯了
I mean, she's talking to me all the time.
她一直跟我说话
Well, no, you gotta stick up for yourself, all right?
不  这不是你的责任 懂吗?
- I know. - You can't expect every...
- 我知道   - 你不能指望每个...
What was that?
那是什么?
Well, it came from that direction.
从那个方向来的
Fuck!
操!
Man, you scared the shit out of me.
伙计 你吓死我了
Oh, what is it? The spooks got you spooked?
哦 怎么了? 黑鬼把你吓着了?
It's nothing, man.
那儿没东西 伙计
There's no one out here this late.
这么晚谁还会在这里
Look at that moon, though. Beautiful.
看那月亮 真美
Yeah.
对
Well, enjoy it, snowflake.
好好赏月吧  胆小鬼
Fine, you traitor.
行  你这叛徒
Yeah, yeah, write about it in your diary, Romeo.
对 对 写进你日记吧 罗密欧
I need to piss, man. I'm gonna take a piss.
我想尿尿 伙计 尿一下
Let me get these fucking things off.
让我把水放掉些
Daniel.
丹尼尔
You're not supposed to say my fucking...
你不应该说我...
- Get the damn phone. - Got it.
- 把手机拿着   - 行了
Oh, shit.
该死
Listen, if I don't make it,
听着 如果我没逃出去
the world has to find out about this place.
得让外面知道并找到这里
It has to end tonight.
今晚必须结束
I know there's service at the cabin.
我知道在房子那里有信号
Let's go.
我们回去
Come on.
快
911, what's your emergency?
911 出了什么事?
What's your emergency?
你有什么险情?
My name is Veronica Henley.
我名字是薇罗尼卡 汉莉
I have been kidnapped. There are so many of us here.
我被绑架了 有很多人在这里
We're on some sort of plantation.
我们在某个种植园
I'm sorry, ma'am, you're breaking up.
抱歉 女士 你信号不好
I need you to send help right now.
我要你马上派人过来
Did you say "plantation"?
你刚才说 "种植园"?
Hello? Hello?
喂? 喂?
We need his face to unlock this phone.
我们需要用他的脸来解锁
That's the only way we can send our location.
这是我们发送方位的唯一方法
I got you.
我赞同
No fuckin' loyalty!
一点都不忠诚!
Eden!
艾登!
My name is Veronica!
我真名是薇罗尼卡!
Open your eyes, motherfucker.
睁开眼睛 混蛋
I said, open your motherfuckin' eyes!
我说 他妈给我睁开眼睛!
Hello?
喂?
Nick?
尼克?
V?
薇?
V!
薇!
I'm okay. I'm alive.
我没事 我活着
V, no. No, no, no. Tell me exactly where you are.
薇 不 不 告诉我你的确切位置
I don't know, but I'm getting out.
我不知道 我正在逃出来
Oh, my God. Everyone has been searching for you.
天呐 所有人都在找你
I can't talk right now.
我现在不便说话
I need you to call the police, now. I'm gonna send you a pin.
你帮我报警 我给你发位置
- <i>Mommy!</i> - Oh.
- <i>妈妈!</i> - 哦
- <i>Okay, okay, V. No.</i> - Baby.
- <i>好的 薇 别...</i> - 宝贝
- <i>No, stay with me.</i> - I love...
- <i>别挂断</i>   - 我爱...
Hello?
喂?
Come on. No. No, no, no.
快点  别 别  别
Professor.
教授
I'm sorry.
对不起
This doesn't end here.
这事没完
We're nowhere
我们来去无踪
and everywhere.
又无处不在
What the fuck are you doin' out of your cabin?
你特么在屋子外面干嘛?
It's the general, sir. He's hurt.
是将军 长官 他受伤了
- Please come quick. - Wait.
- 快来   - 等等
- Come quick. He's hurt. - God!
- 快来 他受伤了   - 上帝!
Oh, God. Oh.
哦 上帝
Jesus Christ. Senator?
上帝啊  参议员?
Senator Denton! Sir?
丹顿参议员 长官?
Eden! Hey! Eden?
艾登! 嘿! 艾登?
Eden, open this door!
艾登, 把门打开!
Shh.
嘘
Please, open the fuckin' door.
把门打开
Open the door. Jesus fuckin'...
开门 真他妈...
Eden, open this fuckin' door right now!
艾登, 马上给我开门!
Open the door!
开门!
No, Veronica!
不 薇罗尼卡!
Veronica, Veronica, listen to me.
薇罗尼卡 薇罗尼卡 听我说
Please. Veronica!
求你 薇罗尼卡!
What the fuck is she doing?
她特么想干嘛?
Open that fuckin' door!
给我把门打开!
No! Get it off!
不! 把火弄灭!
The hell is that?
见鬼是什么?
Go on, mount up! Let's go!
快来 上马! 我们走!
Get, girl! Get!
驾  驾!
Get, girl!
驾!
Eden!
艾登!
Get, girl!
驾!
Eden!
艾登!
You're not gonna get out of here alive.
你不可能活着逃出去
Now, why can't you just accept that?
怎么想不明白呢?
Accept what you are.
认命吧你
You are nothin'.
你什么都不是
You ain't nothin', but a cotton picker.
你贱命一条 只是个采棉工
You think you're better than us,
你觉得比我们好
but you ain't better than me, you fuckin' cunt!
再好好不过我 你这婊子!
My father kept insistin'.
我父亲反复说
He said you were spreadin' such filth!
他说你在宣扬谬论!
I told him you weren't worth the risk,
我告诉他 你不值得去冒险
but he couldn't resist.
但他无法抗拒
The movement be damned!
这行动被诅咒了!
He just had to have you.
他对你势在必得
Every single one of you I picked,
你们每个人 都是我选的
except for you.
除了你
His favorite girl.
他最爱的女孩
Now, of course, like always,
而如今 当然 事情总这样
it's up to a woman to clean up the mess of a man.
要由女人来替男人擦屁股
Eden?
艾登?
Get your black ass out here!
给我滚出来!
Get the fuck up.
给我起来
Get the fuck up!
给我起来!
What kind of woman are you?
你是个什么样的女人?
Get, girl, Get.
驾  驾
Go, Daphne. Get, girl.
快跑  达芙妮  驾
罗伯特 李
总司令官
美利坚联盟国
路易斯安那 首屈一指
内战场景再现公园
闲人勿扰
违者必究
布莱克 丹顿
所有
内战前
English Subtitles: explosiveskull
中文字幕/特效字幕: MeGustaVerano C.X.